I can't believe our first day at MIT!
MJ, come on, pretend like you're not the happiest
you've ever been in your entire life.
I can't.
Ah, I knew it!
Hi, my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me, but we used to know each
other.
Something bad was gonna happen, and the only way to
stop it was to make everyone forget
about me.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
What
the hell, Frank?
You just hit me with a van!
Put your web ring on.
Suit yourself.
Motherfucker!
Go home!
And sometimes Spider-Man has to do the hard thing,
even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
What is happening to me?
Oh God!
Excuse me, Dr.
Banner, I need your help.
What'd you say your name was?
If DNA is mutating, it would be enormously
dangerous.
Spiders have 3 life cycles.
When between cycles, it
can leave the spider vulnerable to threats.
We are faced with a danger that we can't control.
One we can't even see.
Stay out of my way.
You're losing it, kid.
And for those spiders who make it through, it
amounts to a kind of rebirth.
Nice flowers.
Oh, they're, uh, a housewarming gift.
I'm MJ.
I'm just a Neighbor from across the hall.
Friendly neighbor.
Cough.